LOVLEENA SHARMA

B-161, top floor, Freedom Fighter Enclave Sainik Farms, New Delhi - 110068 8285354608 | lovleenasharma49@gmail.com

Objective

As a licensed clinical psychologist with 4 years of experience, I am seeking a challenging and rewarding position where I can apply my expertise in assessment to help individuals achieve optimal mental health. With a passion for providing evidence-based therapy and a commitment to ongoing professional development, I am dedicated to improving lives through a collaborative and compassionate approach.

Experience

 Institute of Human Behaviour and Allied Sciences (IHBAS) September 2020 - Present Clinical Psychologist Trinity Institute of Professional Studies, Dwarka January 2020 - August 2020 Clinical Psychologist Consultant Clinical Psychologist October 2019 - December 2019 Roar Wellness, Chhatarpur Institute of Human Behaviour and Allied Sciences Intern • Civil Hospital, Gurugram Clinical Trainee Citizen Hospital, Gurugram Clinical Trainee • Earth Saviour's Foundation, Bandhwari, Haryana

• Administered Cognitive Assessments at Deep Ashram, Gurugram.

Motilal Nehru College, University of Delhi

- Administered Clinical Assessments and Brief therapy sessions at various fire station in Gurugram.
- Actively involved with Deeksha School, Gurugram for the assessment and treatment of Behavioural Concerns.
- Actively involved with Samarpan Foundation, Gurugram for Assessment and Therapy of Children

Education

Clinical Trainee

	B.A. Political Science (Hons.) 58%	
•	Indira Gandhi National Open University M.A. Psychology 76%	2016
•	Amity University, Gurugram M.phil Clinical Psychology (RCI recognized A66045) 7.83 CGPA	2019

2014

Skills

- Psychotherapy
- · Relaxation Therapy
- · Time management
- Leadership
- · Anger Management
- · Crisis Resolution

Projects

- Satisfaction in job, anxiety and medium of coping in mental healthcare experts, International Journal of Social Sciences Review 2019, Volume 7, issue 5- II, May 2019
- Research paper on Internet Addiction, International Journal of Social Sciences review, 2019

Workshops/ Seminars Conducted

- · Conducted Workshop on exam stress management at Ryan International School, Gurugram, 2019
- Facilitated talk at Aviva Life insurance company and brief therapy sessions on Stress management for the female employees on Women's day, 2019